Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
News Service Biographical Files circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. News Service.
183 linear feet
Duke University. University Archives
The Duke News Service informs the public and the university community about research, programs, and events at Duke. The collection consists of biographical files of Duke University faculty, staff, alumni, and others compiled by the News Service. The files contain primarily clippings and also curricula vitae, photographs, and other printed materials. English.
UA.27.01.0003
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
No restrictions.
Provenance
The News Service Biographical Files were received by the University Archives as transfers in 1991-1995, and 2004.
Historical Note
Formerly known as the News Bureau or News Office. Around 1922, Henry Belk, Class of 1923, was named director of the Trinity News Service. In 1935, the News Service became part of a re-organized Department of Public Relations and Alumni Affairs, with Henry R. Dwire as overall Director. A.A. Wilkinson managed the News Service. Clarence Whitfield was appointed Director of the Bureau of Public Information in 1956, and Director of the Office of Information Services in 1963. This appointment presumably came about as a result of an analysis and appraisal of the University's public relations systems done by the Barton Gillet Company at that time.
The mission of the Duke News Service is to inform the public and the university community about research, programs, and events at Duke; to increase public understanding and appreciation of scholarly contributions made by Duke's faculty and the work of its other employees and students; and to provide media relations and consultative services to faculty and administrators. The Duke News Service works closely with local, national, and international news media, including newspapers, radio and television, magazines, wire services and syndicates.
Collection Overview
The collection consists of biographical files of Duke University faculty, staff, alumni, and others compiled by the News Service. The files contain primarily clippings and also curricula vitae, photographs, and other printed materials.
Subject Headings
Duke University. News Service; Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- Students
Related Material
University Archives Biographical Files.
University Archives, Duke University.
News Service Subject Files.
University Archives, Duke University.
News Service Press Releases and Clippings.
University Archives, Duke University.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Container List:
  - Abbey, W.D. (Box 1)
  - Abeles, Paul W. (Box 1)
  - Abt, Arthur (Box 1)
  - Acomb, Frances, 1907-1984 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Anne H., -1980 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Donald Keith 1902-1971 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Edward L., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Adams, James L. (Box 1)
  - Addoms, Ruth M. (Box 1)
  - Adler, Alexandria (Box 1)
  - Agawu, Kofi V. (Box 1)
  - Agnello, Sam (Box 1)
  - Agres, J.P. (Box 1)
  - Ainsworth, Charles C. (Box 1)
  - Aldridge, F.S. (Box 1)
  - Aldridge, Thomas A. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Irving (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Leo (Box 1)
  - Allen, Clark Lee (Box 1)
  - Allen, D.C. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Gay (Box 1)
  - Allen, George V. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Richard Harry (Box 1)
  - Altman, Richard (Box 1)
  - Altrocchi, John (Box 1)
  - Altvater, F. Vernon (Box 1)
  - Alyea, Edwin Pascal (Box 1)
  - Amore, Thomas (Box 1)
  - Amoss, Harold L. (Box 1)
  - Anastasion, Nicholas (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Andrew R. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Charles Roberts (Box 1)
  - Anderson, David E. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Hugh (Box 1)
  - Anderson, James Willis (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Lewis Edward (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Robert W. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Roger E. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, William Banks (Box 1)
  - Andreoli, Thomas E. (Box 1)
  - Andrewartha, Herbert G. (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Kree (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Lee (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Samuel W. II (Box 1)
  - Apgar, Lawrence Clarke (Box 1)
  - Appel, Stanley H. (Box 1)
  - Aquila, Richard E. (Box 1)
  - Archie, Dean (Box 1)
  - Archie, William C. (Box 1)
  - Arena, Jay M. (Box 1)
  - Arges, K. Pete (Box 1)
  - Arnold, Ralph (Box 1)
  - Artley, John L. (Box 1)
  - Aschoff, Jurgen W. (Box 1)
  - Ashbrook, Arthur G., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Ashe, John Rainey, Jr. (Box 1)
  - Ashmore, Frank L. (Box 1)
  - Athos, Ottolenghi (Box 1)
  - Attebery, Jesse S., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Atwood, Theodore W. (Box 1)
  - Aubery, Pierre L. (Box 1)
  - Auerbach, David Alan (Box 1)
  - Auld, Louis Eugene (Box 1)
  - Aumiller, Richard B. (Box 1)
  - Avery, George S., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Aviles, Luis, Jr. (Box 1)
  - Aycock, Thomas A. (Box 1)
  - Ayers, Erle Bingham (Box 1)
  - Aylor, Oscar R. (Box 1)
  - Baade, Hans W. (Box 1)
  - Babour, George B. (Box 1)
  - Baier, Roger W. (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Joseph H. (Box 1)
  - Bain, Barbara (Box 2)
  - Baker, Bessie (Box 2)
  - Baker, Frank (Box 2)
  - Baker, Kenneth Robert (Box 2)
  - Baker, Lennox D. (Box 2)
  - Baker, Maury Davidson (Box 2)
  - Baker, Roger D. (Box 2)
  - Baldwin, Alice M. (Box 2)
  - Baley, James A. (Box 2)
  - Ball, Margaret (Box 2)
  - Ballard, Bruce W. (Box 2)
  - Banham, Kathrine May (Box 2)
  - Banks, Eugene (Box 2)
  - Barefoot, Sherwood W. (Box 2)
  - Barlow, Norman Howard (Box 2)
  - Barker, Ruth E. (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Evelyn (Box 2)
  - Barnes, J. Foster (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Myrtle Preyer (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Robert D. (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Robert H. (Box 2)
  - Barnhart, Francis E. (Box 2)
  - Barry, William F. (Box 2)
  - Bartlett, Robert B. (Box 2)
  - Bass, Reiner (Box 2)
  - Bassett, John Spencer (Box 2)
  - Bassett, Robert V. R., Jr. (Box 2)
  - Baum, Paul Franklin (Box 2)
  - Baum, Walter P. (Box 2)
  - Baxley, John V. (Box 2)
  - Baylin, George J. (Box 2)
  - Baylis, Charles A. (Box 2)
  - Baysinger, Reaves H. (Box 2)
  - Beach, W. Waldo (Box 2)
  - Beal, James A. (Box 2)
  - Beals, Richard (Box 2)
  - Bear, Warren C. (Box 2)
  - Beard, Joseph W. (Box 2)
  - Bearman, Dale Michael (Box 2)
  - Beatty, I. Croom (Box 2)
  - Beaudreau, George S. (Box 2)
  - Becker, R. Frederick (Box 2)
  - Bell, Gordon E. (Box 2)
  - Bell, Wilhelmina (Box 2)
  - Bellows, Rowland T. (Box 2)
  - Benedict, Barbara (Box 2)
  - Bennett, Paul R. (Box 2)
  - Bentley, Peter J. (Box 2)
  - Benton, John K. (Box 2)
  - Berblinger, Klaus W. (Box 2)
  - Beres, William Philip (Box 2)
  - Bergland, John K. (Box 2)
  - Berkley, Kenneth H. (Box 2)
  - Bernheim, Frederick (Box 2)
  - Bernheim, Mary Lilas Christian (Box 2)
  - Berninger, Oscar August (Box 2)
  - Berry, E. Wollard (Box 2)
  - Berry, Lucia K. (Box 2)
  - Berry, Thomas (Box 2)
  - Best, Thomas W. (Box 2)
  - Bestebruertje, Annie M. (Box 2)
  - Bethea, Joseph Benjamin (Box 2)
  - Beveridge, David L. (Box 3)
  - Bevington, Helen (Box 3)
  - Bevington, Merle M. (Box 3)
  - Biddle, Mary Duke (Box 3)
  - Bier, Justus (Box 3)
  - Bigelow, Lucius A. (Box 3)
  - Billig, Otto (Box 3)
  - Billig, Thomas Clifford (Box 3)
  - Billings, William Dwight (Box 3)
  - Bindewald, Richard Andrew (Box 3)
  - Binkley, Margaret (Box 3)
  - Binkley, Robert W. (Box 3)
  - Bird, Harold C. (Box 3)
  - Birley, Anthony R. (Box 3)
  - Black, Julian R. (Box 3)
  - Black, Martin Lee, Jr. (Box 3)
  - Blackburn, William Maxwell (Box 3)
  - Blakely, Florence Ella (Box 3)
  - Blaydon, Colin C. (Box 3)
  - Bleck, Eugene E. (Box 3)
  - Black-Schaffer, Bernard (Box 3)
  - Block, Martin M. (Box 3)
  - Blomquist, Hugo Leander (Box 3)
  - Bloor, Byran Michel (Box 3)
  - Blum, Jay (Box 3)
  - Bly, Chauncey G. (Box 3)
  - Bly, James R. (Box 3)
  - Boas, Mary Layne (Box 3)
  - Boas, Ralph (Box 3)
  - Bocchino, Anthony J. (Box 3)
  - Bock, George E. (Box 3)
  - Bogdonoff, Morton D. (Box 3)
  - Boineau, John (Box 3)
  - Boletta, William L. (Box 3)
  - Boles, Thomas D. (Box 3)
  - Bolich, William Bryan (Box 3)
  - Bolmeier, Edward C. (Box 3)
  - Bonar, Robert A. (Box 3)
  - Bone, Alan (2) (Box 3)
  - Bonk, Johan P. (Box 3)
  - Bonner, Lyman (Box 3)
  - Bookhout, Cazlyn G. (Box 4)
  - Bookhout, Elizabeth C. (Box 4)
  - Boone, Charles C. (Box 4)
  - Booth, Rachel Z. (Box 4)
  - Borstleman, Lloyd J. (Box 4)
  - Bosley, Harold A. (Box 4)
  - Bost, Thomas C. (Box 4)
  - Boudewyns, Patrick Alan (Box 4)
  - Boughton, James (Box 4)
  - Bourgeois-Gavardin, Michel (Box 4)
  - Bouton, Margaret (Box 4)
  - Bowden, Bill (Box 4)
  - Bowen, Alva Manly (Box 4)
  - Bower, Harvey (Box 4)
  - Bowers, H.F. (Box 4)
  - Bowman, Francis E. (Box 4)
  - Boyarsky, Saul (Box 4)
  - Boyce, Benjamin (Box 4)
  - Boyd, Robert (Box 4)
  - Boyd, William Kenneth (Box 4)
  - Boyer, John Strickland (Box 4)
  - Boyle, T.A. (Box 4)
  - Braaten, Melvin O. (Box 4)
  - Bradley, Harold L. (Box 4)
  - Bradley, Mike (Box 4)
  - Bradsher, Charles K., (4 folders) (Box 4)
  - Bradway, John Saeyer (Box 5)
  - Brame, Robert G. (Box 5)
  - Brandenburg, Arthur Lewis. (Box 5)
  - Brandis, Royall (Box 5)
  - Brandwajn, Alexandre (Box 5)
  - Branscomb, Bennett Harvie (Box 5)
  - Braswell, Charles M. (Box 5)
  - Brauer, Ralph (Box 5)
  - Brazy, Jane Embald. (Box 5)
  - Breedlove, Joseph Penn (Box 5)
  - Breen, Patrick J. (Box 5)
  - Brees, Anton, (2 Folders) (Box 5)
  - Brehm, Jack Williams (Box 5)
  - Bressler, Rubin (Box 5)
  - Breswick, William N. (Box 5)
  - Brewster, Lawrence Fay (Box 5)
  - Brice, Ashbel Green (Box 5)
  - Bridgers, Furman A. (Box 5)
  - Brieger, Gert H. (Box 5)
  - Brinkley, Roberta F. (Box 5)
  - Brinkley, William L. (Box 5)
  - Britt, Ann (Box 5)
  - Broadbent, Thomas Ray (Box 5)
  - Broadfoot, Winston (Box 5)
  - Broadhead, Edward Hall (Box 5)
  - Broce, Thomas E. (Box 5)
  - Brocker, Edith Perryman (Box 5)
  - Broderson, Robert M. (Box 5)
  - Brogan, Wesley (Box 5)
  - Bromage, Philip Raikes (Box 5)
  - Bromberg, Michael D. (Box 5)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Martin (Box 5)
  - Brooks, Elmer Leroy (Box 6)
  - Brooks, Eugene Clyde (Box 6)
  - Broughton, T. R. S. (Box 6)
  - Brouse, Albert J. (Box 6)
  - Brower, Albert Smith (Box 6)
  - Brown, Brenda (Box 6)
  - Brown, Chandler Wilcox (Box 6)
  - Brown, Earl F. (Box 6)
  - Brown, Frances Campbell (Box 6)
  - Brown, Frank Clyde (Box 6)
  - Brown, Herbert Ross (Box 6)
  - Brown, Dr .Ivan (Box 6)
  - Brown, Montague (Box 6)
  - Brown, Myrtle Irene (Box 6)
  - Brown, Ray Everett, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Brown, Robert G. (Box 6)
  - Brown, Thuretta (Box 6)
  - Brown, Wade Gillies (Box 6)
  - Brownell, William Arthur (Box 6)
  - Brownlee, William Hugh (Box 6)
  - Brucker, Edward Byerly (Box 6)
  - Bruinsma, Henry A. (Box 6)
  - Brukman, Jan (Box 6)
  - Brumley, George W. (Box 6)
  - Brusie, Richard C. (Box 6)
  - Bruton, Paul W. (Box 6)
  - Bryan, Edward H. (Box 6)
  - Bryan, Paul Robey, Jr., (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Bryan, William A. (Box 6)
  - Bryant, Joseph Allen (Box 6)
  - Bryson, E.C. (Box 7)
  - Bryson, Marion R. (Box 7)
  - Bryson, Thaddeus D. (Box 7)
  - Bubas, Victor Albert, (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Buck, Johannes (Box 7)
  - Buck, Roger C. (Box 7)
  - Buckheit, George C. (Box 7)
  - Buckingham, M. J. (Box 7)
  - Buckley, James C. (Box 7)
  - Buckner, Edward R. (Box 7)
  - Buettner-Janusch, John (Box 7)
  - Burger, Michael J. (Box 7)
  - Burger, Wilbert (Bud) E. (Box 7)
  - Burgess, Mary (Box 7)
  - Burkholder, Peter M. (Box 7)
  - Burlak, Jacob (Box 7)
  - Busse, Ewald, (5 Folders) (Box 7)
  - Butler, Edmund (Box 7)
  - Butler, Joseph D. (Box 7)
  - Butterfield, Barbara S. (Box 7)
  - Caddell, Elinor (Box 7)
  - Cady, Edwin Harrison (Box 7)
  - Cahoon, John B., Jr. (Box 7)
  - Cairns, Michael (Box 7)
  - Caldwell, Sam Johnston (Box 7)
  - Calkins, Philip B. (Box 7)
  - Callcott, Wilfrid H. (Box 7)
  - Calloway, J. Lamar (Box 7)
  - Cameron, E.M. (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Janet (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Mary B. (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Michael Ian (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Richard T. (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Sullivan Graham (Box 8)
  - Camporesi, Enrico M. (Box 8)
  - Canine, William (Box 8)
  - Cannon, James, III. (Box 8)
  - Capp, M. Paul (Box 8)
  - Card, Wilbur Wade (Box 8)
  - Carden, Norman F., Jr. (Box 8)
  - Carlitz, Leonard (Box 8)
  - Carlton, John W. (Box 8)
  - Carpenter, David Williams (Box 8)
  - Carpenter, Dwight W. (Box 8)
  - Carpenter, James M. (Box 8)
  - Carr, John W., Jr. (Box 8)
  - Carroll, Gilbert (Box 8)
  - Carroll, Malcolm E. (Box 8)
  - Carroll, Jackson W. (Box 8)
  - Carroll, Robert S. (Box 8)
  - Carter, Bayard, (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Carter, James G. (Box 8)
  - Cartter, Allan Murray (Box 8)
  - Castallano, Juan R. (Box 8)
  - Cathcart, A.M. (Box 8)
  - Cattell, Raymond Bernard (Box 8)
  - Cavaliere, A. Ralph (Box 8)
  - Cavanaugh, G.S. Terrence (Box 8)
  - Cavanaugh, Patrick J. (Box 8)
  - Cavers, David F. (Box 8)
  - Chaffin, Nora Campbell (Box 8)
  - Chaiken, Leon Edward (Box 8)
  - Chamberlain, Hope Summerell (Box 8)
  - Chambers, Robert Luther (Box 8)
  - Chapman, Norman B. (Box 8)
  - Chapman, Robert G. (Box 8)
  - Charlesworth, James H., (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Chase, Lewis (Box 9)
  - Cheek, Mrs. Roma S. (Box 9)
  - Cheney, Margaret (Box 9)
  - Chernoff, Amoz I. (Box 9)
  - Cherny, Walter (Box 9)
  - Cherpack, Clifton (Box 9)
  - Childs, Benjamin Guy, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Christ, Robert W. (Box 9)
  - Christian, Charles, II. (Box 9)
  - Church, Austin H. (Box 9)
  - Church, Margaret (Box 9)
  - Cianciolo, George (Box 9)
  - Ciompi, Giorgio, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Clark, Edgar William (Box 9)
  - Clark, Kenneth Willis, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Clark, Lelia (Box 9)
  - Clark, Robert W. (Box 9)
  - Clarke, Edmund Melson, Jr. (Box 9)
  - Clarke, Maurice (Box 9)
  - Clarke-Pearson, Daniel L. (Box 10)
  - Clausen, Joy Carol Princeton (Box 10)
  - Clay, Captain Alfred Thomas (Box 10)
  - Clay, Susan (Box 10)
  - Cleland, James T., (5 folders) (Box 10)
  - Cleveland, Louise (Box 10)
  - Cleveland, William Porter, Jr. (Box 10)
  - Clifford, Paul (Box 10)
  - Clogan, Paul Maurice (Box 10)
  - Clubbe, John (Box 10)
  - Clugston, George Alan (Box 10)
  - Clyde, Paul (Box 10)
  - Cobb, Clarence Harper (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Louis D. (Box 10)
  - Cohen, Sanford I. (Box 10)
  - Coile, Theodore Stanley (Box 10)
  - Cole, R. Taylor, (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Colver, Robert Merle (Box 11)
  - Conant, Norman F. (Box 11)
  - Conner, William E. (Box 11)
  - Connery, Robert H. (Box 11)
  - Conover, Richard M. (Box 11)
  - Conrad, Cecilia (Box 11)
  - Conrad, Robert (Box 11)
  - Constant, Frank Woodbridge (Box 11)
  - Convery, Frank J. (Box 11)
  - Cook, Clark Curtis (Box 11)
  - Cook, Samuel Dubois (Box 11)
  - Coombs, John Wesley, (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Cooney, James P. (Box 11)
  - Corbett, W. Horace (Box 11)
  - Corker, Lottie C. (Box 11)
  - Correll, Donovan S. (Box 11)
  - Corrie, Bruce A. (Box 11)
  - Cotanch, Patricia H. (Box 11)
  - Cotton, William J.H. (Box 11)
  - Covington, Mary Simmons (Box 11)
  - Covington, Ned (Box 11)
  - Cowper, Frederick Augustus Grant (Box 11)
  - Cox, Robert Boyd (Box 11)
  - Cranford, William Ivey (Box 11)
  - Craven, Leslie (Box 11)
  - Craven, R. Braxton (Box 11)
  - Creadick, Robert N. (Box 11)
  - Crenshaw, M. Carlyle (Box 11)
  - Cress, Hertha R. (Box 11)
  - Crispell, Raymond (Box 11)
  - Croker, Byron Pennington (Box 11)
  - Crossland, Fred E. (Box 11)
  - Crotwell, Helen (Box 11)
  - Crowell, John Franklin (Box 11)
  - Crum, Mason (Box 12)
  - Cunninggim, Merrimon (Box 12)
  - Cunningham, Bert (Box 12)
  - Currie, Brainerd (Box 12)
  - Curtiss, John Shelton (Box 12)
  - Cushman, Robert Earl (Box 12)
  - Daffner, Richard Howard (Box 12)
  - Dai, Bingham (Box 12)
  - Dajani, Jarir S. (Box 12)
  - Dale, Julia (Box 12)
  - Daly, Charles J. (Box 12)
  - Dana, William J. (Box 12)
  - Daniels, Boyd Lee (Box 12)
  - Dann, William John (Box 12)
  - Danzon, Patricia (Box 12)
  - Darkis, Frederick R. (Box 12)
  - Darrow, Susan E. (Box 12)
  - Daston, Paul George (Box 12)
  - Davidson, Eugene (Box 12)
  - Davies, David George (Box 12)
  - Davies, R.N. (Box 12)
  - Davies, William David (Box 12)
  - Davis, Archie K. (Box 12)
  - Davis, Clarence D. (Box 12)
  - Davis, Gifford (Box 12)
  - Davis, Otho L. (Box 12)
  - Davison, Wilburt Cornell, (7 folders) (Box 13)
  - Dawson, John W. (Box 13)
  - Dawson, Percy M. (Box 13)
  - Dean, Dayton (Box 13)
  - Dean, Gordon Evans (Box 13)
  - Dearlove, Judith Elizabeth (Box 13)
  - Debrunner, Hans E. (Box 13)
  - Decker, Peter R. (Box 13)
  - DeConde, Alexander (Box 13)
  - Dees, Susan Coons (Box 13)
  - DeGravelles, William D. (Box 13)
  - De Hart, James (Box 13)
  - DeJong, Herman (Box 13)
  - Delaplane, Walter Harold (Box 13)
  - Delcher, Harry K. (Box 13)
  - DeMaria, William (Box 13)
  - Demorest, Jean-Jacques (Box 13)
  - Dent, Sara J. (Box 13)
  - De Turk, William Ernest (Box 13)
  - Detwiler, John C. (Box 13)
  - Deubner, David C. (Box 13)
  - Devitto, John (Box 13)
  - DeVries, Walter (Box 14)
  - DeVries, William (Box 14)
  - Dewey, Donald (Box 14)
  - DeWitt, Maree (Box 14)
  - DeVyvor, Frank Trevor (Box 14)
  - Di Cecco, Luca (Box 14)
  - Dick, Macdonald (Box 14)
  - Dick, D.A.T. (Box 14)
  - Dickens, Robert L. (Box 14)
  - Di Corcia, Joseph (Box 14)
  - Dicks, Rev. Russell L., (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Di Perna, Ronald J. (Box 14)
  - Dillon, Marcus Lunsford (Box 14)
  - Dimmitt, Luther Mason (Box 14)
  - Dittman, David A. (Box 14)
  - Djordjevic, Milan (Box 14)
  - Donegan, Charles K. (Box 14)
  - Douglas, Craig C. (Box 14)
  - Douglass, Fenner (Box 14)
  - Douthat, James (Box 14)
  - Dovenmuehle, Robert (Box 14)
  - Dow, Mme. Marie (Box 14)
  - Dow, Neal (Box 14)
  - Dowling, Mary Louise (Box 14)
  - Doxey, J.E. (Box 14)
  - Dozier, John Marion (Box 14)
  - Drayer, Burton P. (Box 15)
  - Dressel, Francis George (Box 15)
  - Drew, Thomas L. (Box 15)
  - Droege, Robert C. (Box 15)
  - Dubar, Jules R. (Box 15)
  - DuBose, Robert N. (Box 15)
  - Dubs, Homer H. (Box 15)
  - Duffy, Bernard (Box 15)
  - Duke, Angier Biddle (Box 15)
  - Duke, Anthony Drexel (Box 15)
  - Duke, Benjamin N., (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Duke, James B., (2 folders) (Box 15)
  - Duke, Kenneth L. (Box 15)
  - Duke, Washington (Box 15)
  - Dukes, Charles A. (Box 15)
  - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing (Box 15)
  - Duncan, Charles H. (Box 15)
  - Duncan, Dale Lemoin (Box 15)
  - Dunlap, Connie R. (Box 15)
  - Dunning, Stephen (Box 15)
  - Dupree, Louis (Box 15)
  - Durant, Edward W., Jr. (Box 15)
  - Durham, Harry (Box 15)
  - Dvorak, Jiri (Box 15)
  - Dwire, Henry Rudolph (Box 15)
  - Dyer, Allen (Box 15)
  - Eadie, George Sharpe (Box 16)
  - Eagle, Watt Weems (Box 16)
  - Easley, Eleanor B. (Box 16)
  - Eckel, Martha Elaine (Box 16)
  - Edens, Hollis, (8 Folders) (Box 16)
  - Edens, Joseph, (2 Folders) (Box 17)
  - Edgerton, F.N. (Box 17)
  - Edwards, Charles William (Box 17)
  - Edwards, Herbert O. (Box 17)
  - Edwards, Ray I. (Box 17)
  - Egorov, Igor Konstantinovich (Box 17)
  - Ehlhardt, George (Box 17)
  - Eisdorfer, Carl (Box 17)
  - Eisenbarth, George S. (Box 17)
  - Eiteman, Wilford J. (Box 17)
  - Elchlepp, Jane G. (Box 17)
  - Elliott, William W. (Box 17)
  - Ellwood, Charles A. (Box 17)
  - Engel, Frank L. (Box 17)
  - Erdberg, Claudia (Box 17)
  - Erickson, Bonnie (Box 17)
  - Erickson, Cyrus C. (Box 17)
  - Eslinger, Richard Lawrence (Box 17)
  - Estes, E. Harvey, (2 Folders) (Box 17)
  - Evans, Evan A. (Box 17)
  - Everett, John Wendall (Box 17)
  - Everett, Robinson O. (Box 17)
  - Evers, Mark (Box 17)
  - Fabian, Leonard (Box 17)
  - Fagraeus, Lennart (Box 17)
  - Fahrner, Lester (Box 17)
  - Fairbank, Henry A. (Box 17)
  - Fairbank, William M. (Box 17)
  - Falcone, Carmen (Box 17)
  - Fearing, Robert (Box 17)
  - Fedak, Michael (Box 18)
  - Feezor, Allen Daniel (Box 18)
  - Fellows, Robert E., Jr. (Box 18)
  - Fendt, Paul F. (Box 18)
  - Fenton, Charles A. (Box 18)
  - Ferguson, Arthur Bowles (Box 18)
  - Ferguson, Charles E. (Box 18)
  - Ferguson, George B. (Box 18)
  - Ferrari, Heriberto Alfredo (Box 18)
  - Ferrell, Jesse W. (Box 18)
  - Fetters, James C. (Box 18)
  - Few, William Preston, (4 Folders) (Box 18)
  - Fike, Edward L. (Box 18)
  - Fillmore, Paul G. (Box 18)
  - Fillmore, Richard (Box 18)
  - Finnell, Dallas G. (Box 18)
  - First, Joan (Box 18)
  - Fishbaugh, Ronald L. (Box 18)
  - Fisher, Edgar Jacob (Box 18)
  - Fisher, John H. (Box 18)
  - Fitzgerald, William Stone (Box 18)
  - Fjeld, Jon (Box 18)
  - Flanagan, Eleanor (Box 18)
  - Flint, Weston (Box 18)
  - Flowers, Anne (Box 18)
  - Flowers, Robert Lee, (3 Folders) (Box 18)
  - Floyd, W. Harvey (Box 19)
  - Foeckler, Merle M. (Box 19)
  - Foerster, Norman (Box 19)
  - Follis, Richard (Box 19)
  - Folsom, James W. (Box 19)
  - Folsom, Reid (Box 19)
  - Forbus, Wiley D. (Box 19)
  - Ford, Joel C. (Box 19)
  - Fortney, Lloyd (Box 19)
  - Foster, Andrew Durwood (Box 19)
  - Foster, Bill (Box 19)
  - Fowler, Earle C. (Box 19)
  - Fowler, John A. (Box 19)
  - Fowler, Marshall (Box 19)
  - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 19)
  - Fox, Adrienne (Box 19)
  - Fox, John W. (Box 19)
  - Frarey, Carlyle (Box 19)
  - Freeman, John (Box 19)
  - Freiburghouse, Leonard F. (Box 19)
  - Frenzel, Charles, Jr. (Box 19)
  - Freundlich, Irwin (Box 19)
  - Friedberg, Ruth (Box 19)
  - Friedberg, Samuel (Box 19)
  - Friedlander, Walter (Box 19)
  - Friedman, Gregg A. (Box 19)
  - Friedrich, John A., (2 Folders) (Box 19)
  - Frye, John (Box 19)
  - Funderburk, Laney (Box 19)
  - Furbish, William James (Box 19)
  - Furlow, John A. (Box 19)
  - Fuson, Robert L. (Box 19)
  - Gaffron, Mercedes (Box 19)
  - Gall, Stanley (Box 19)
  - Gallagher, James J. (Box 19)
  - Gallemore, John (Box 19)
  - Garber, Paul, (2 Folders) (Box 19)
  - Gardiner, Ann Henshaw (Box 19)
  - Gardner, Clarence E., Jr. (Box 19)
  - Garmezy, Norman (Box 20)
  - Garrard, Anne (Box 20)
  - Gates, Arthur Mathews (Box 20)
  - Gatling, Eva Ingersoll (Box 20)
  - Gauer, Otto Hans (Box 20)
  - Gehman, Ila (Box 20)
  - Gehman, W. Scott (Box 20)
  - Geist, Robert M., III (Box 20)
  - Gellhorn, Ernest A.E. (Box 20)
  - Gentry, William Doyle (Box 20)
  - Gerber, Gerald E. (Box 20)
  - Gergen, John J. (Box 20)
  - Gerhard, Hans W. (Box 20)
  - German, Deborah Campano (Box 20)
  - German, Lawrence D. (Box 20)
  - Germino, Barbara (Box 20)
  - Gerstle, Frank (Box 20)
  - Giannini, Richard C. (Box 20)
  - Giannitrapani, Duilio (Box 20)
  - Gibson, Jan (Box 20)
  - Gibson, William Marion (Box 20)
  - Gilbert, Allan (Box 20)
  - Gilbert, Katherine Everett (Box 20)
  - Gili, Mary Eidam (Mrs. Torrence A.) (Box 20)
  - Gillen, Paul N. (Box 20)
  - Gillespie, Richard A. (Box 20)
  - Gillin, Donald (Box 20)
  - Gillin, John P. (Box 20)
  - Gillmore, George W. (Box 20)
  - Ginn, Fred L. (Box 20)
  - Gionta, Ralph L. (Box 20)
  - Giraldo, Zaida I. (Box 20)
  - Githens, Sherwood (Box 20)
  - Glasson, John (Box 20)
  - Glasson, William Henry (Box 20)
  - Glenn, James F. (Box 20)
  - Glockler, George (Box 20)
  - Gobbel, Ellen Huckabee (Box 20)
  - Godbey, Allen H. (Box 20)
  - Goffen, Rona (Box 20)
  - Gohdes, Clarence (Box 20)
  - Goldberg, Leon (Box 21)
  - Goldin, Judah (Box 21)
  - Goldner, J. Leonard (Box 21)
  - Goldsmith, Jewett (Box 21)
  - Goldsmith, Lowell A. (Box 21)
  - Goldstone, Sanford (Box 21)
  - Goodall, McChesney, Jr. (Box 21)
  - Goodling, Richard A. (Box 21)
  - Goodrich, Jack (Box 21)
  - Gordy, Walter, (2 Folders) (Box 21)
  - Goree, John A. (Box 21)
  - Graham, Lindsay Alexander (Box 21)
  - Graham, Tom (Box 21)
  - Grant, Richard Babson (Box 21)
  - Graves, Robert Williams (Box 21)
  - Gray, Edward Rutherford (Box 21)
  - Gray, Irving Emery (Box 21)
  - Gray, Robert Earl (Box 21)
  - Green, C. Sylvester (Box 21)
  - Green, William L. (Box 21)
  - Greene, Ronald H. (Box 21)
  - Greenhill, Maurice H. (Box 21)
  - Greer, Paul S. (Box 21)
  - Gregg, Robert A. (Box 21)
  - Gregg, Robert C. (Box 21)
  - Greuling, Eugene (Box 21)